

Detail & Contact

Age of Birth, Oct 17 2000



alfiadhiputra.business@gmail.com



085801311623



alfiadhiputra.github.io

Education

2015 - 2019

Software Engineering SMK Islam Al Alamanah Salem

2021 - Now

Informatics Study Program Amikom Purwokerto University

Expertise

| Adobe Photoshop | 80% |
|--------------------|-----|
| Adobe Illustrator | 75% |
| Figma | 90% |
| Corel Draw | 60% |
| Adobe Premiere Pro | 75% |
| Adobe After Effect | 70% |

Alfiadhi Putra

UI/UX Designer















About Me

I am a dedicated Graphic Designer, specializing in UI/UX Design, with an active role as a Content Creator across various social media platforms including YouTube, Instagram, and TikTok. Currently, I am pursuing a degree in Computer Engineering at Amikom Purwokerto University, where I am honing my skills in innovative web-based application development.

Work Experience

SMK Islam Al Amanah Salem

Computer Technician | 2019 - 2021

- Working as an employee in an educational institution
- Working in the management and maintenance section of a computer laboratory (technician)
- and teaches in the field of computer science

Youtube

Content Creator 2017 - Now

Ultrices proin elit, tellus euismod. Leo id volutpat cursus integer faucibus ultrices. Convallis ipsum eu adipiscing lorem.

Organizational Experience

INTERMEDIA

Member 2021 - 2022

Join an intermedia organization as a member in the multimedia field.



Detail & Contact

Age of Birth, Oct 17 2000

alfiadhiputra.business@gmail.com

085801311623

alfiadhiputra.github.io

Education

2015 - 2019

Software Engineering SMK Islam Al Alamanah Salem

2021 - Now

Informatics Study Program Amikom Purwokerto University

Expertise

| Adobe Photoshop | 80% |
|--------------------|-----|
| Adobe Illustrator | 75% |
| Figma | 90% |
| Corel Draw | 60% |
| Adobe Premiere Pro | 75% |
| Adobe After Effect | 70% |

Alfiadhi Putra

UI/UX Designer

















Bootcamp Program & Sertification

• Skilvul #Tech4Impact Kampus Merdeka Cycle 2023 5: UI/UX Design

• Kickstart Your Front End Developer Career With React JS By Edspert.Id

2023

• For Completing Full-Stack Web Development 101 By Binar Academy

2023

• Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development By Niagahoster

2022

Creative Competition

Festival Video Reels

As 1st Winner In The Competition | 2022

Was selected as the first winner in the video reels festival competition.

Skills

Soft Skills

- Lead & Strategy
- Innovative
- Team Work
- Goal Oriented

Hard Skills

- Creative Design
- Design Thinking
- Copy Writing & Typography

Language

- Indonesian
- English